{
    "subject": "resource/Subhumans_(Canadian_band)",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/Subhumans_(Canadian_band)",
    "human_readable": "Subhumans (Canadian band) has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9873706102371216,
            "question": "Does Subhumans (Canadian band) possess a photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9870550632476807,
            "question": "Is there a photo collection associated with Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9720116257667542,
            "question": "Is there a photo archive belonging to Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9370377063751221,
            "question": "Subhumans (Canadian band) is known for having what type of collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8883858323097229,
            "question": "What does Subhumans (Canadian band) have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8810836672782898,
            "question": "What can be found in the collection of Subhumans (Canadian band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8451961278915405,
            "question": "Does Subhumans (Canadian band) keep a record of their photos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8306034207344055,
            "question": "What do Subhumans (Canadian band) store in their collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8292315006256104,
            "question": "What kind of collection does Subhumans (Canadian band) own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.822674572467804,
            "question": "What kind of media does Subhumans (Canadian band)'s collection consist of?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Subhumans (Canadian band) has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1697_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of collection does Subhumans (Canadian band) own?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1697_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do Subhumans (Canadian band) store in their collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1697_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Subhumans (Canadian band) keep a record of their photos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1697_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1697_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not contain any information about the Subhumans having a photo collection. Therefore, based on the given context, the statement is unsupported and thus incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided suggesting that the Subhumans (Canadian band) has a photo collection.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of a photo collection associated with the Subhumans band in any of the provided text.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context does not mention any photo collection related to the Subhumans band.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}